<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Are you depressed</string>
    <string name="question1">Do you feel sad most of the time?</string>
    <string name="question2">Did you lose interest in most of the enjoyable things for you?</string>
    <string name="question3">Are you always tired, always have low energy and you always struggle to accomplish everything on your daily <b>"to do"</b> list?</string>
    <string name="question4">Is it hard to find the motivation to do anything  including going out with friends or completing tasks?</string>
    <string name="question5">Do you feel anxious and worried about little things in life?</string>
    <string name="question6">Do you have negative thoughts and feelings of anger often playing themselves in your mind?</string>
    <string name="question7">Do you feel restless, irritable and often lash out at the people who are closest to you?</string>
    <string name="question8">Can it be difficult to fall asleep or stay asleep – regardless of how tired you may be?</string>
    <string name="question9">Do you find it\'s hard to concentrate on anything and you are more forgetful than ever?</string>
    <string name="question10">Do you have headaches, backaches, joint pain and other physical ailments that you can’t pin-point the problem and don’t respond to regular treatments?</string>
    <string name="question11">Do you feel Some days that you are sad or guilty about the things you haven’t done?</string>
    <string name="question12">Do you feel lonely even when there is a room full of people around you and often worry that no one really likes you?</string>
    <string name="question13">Have you problems with your weight and you are starting to feel overwhelmed by your own life?</string>
    <string name="question14">Do you have auditory or visual hallucinations ?</string>
    <string name="question15">Did you think of or tried to hurt yourself or commit suicide ?</string>
    <string name="depression">Depression</string>
    <string name="d_description">Depression (major depressive disorder) is a common and serious medical illness that negatively affects how you feel, the way you think and how you act. Fortunately, it is also treatable. Depression causes feelings of sadness and/or a loss of interest in activities once enjoyed. It can lead to a variety of emotional and physical problems and can decrease a person’s ability to function at work and at home.</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="question_1">Question 1 :</string>
    <string name="question_2">Question 2 :</string>
    <string name="question_3">Question 3 :</string>
    <string name="question_4">Question 4 :</string>
    <string name="question_5">Question 5 :</string>
    <string name="question_6">Question 6 :</string>
    <string name="question_7">Question 7 :</string>
    <string name="question_8">Question 8 :</string>
    <string name="question_9">Question 9 :</string>
    <string name="question_10">Question 10 :</string>
    <string name="question_11">Question 11 :</string>
    <string name="question_12">Question 12 :</string>
    <string name="question_13">Question 13 :</string>
    <string name="question_14">Question 14 :</string>
    <string name="question_15">Question 15 :</string>
    <string name="question_16">Question 16 :</string>
    <string name="severe">severe depression</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="answer">Please answer all the questions</string>
    <string name="moderate">Moderate depression</string>
    <string name="not">You aren\'t depressed </string>
    <string name="mild">Mild depression</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="test">I\'m ready to take the Quiz</string>
    <string name="are_you_ready">Are you ready to take the Quiz !?</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="arabic">العربية</string>
</resources>
